The most powerful
are not above the law.
Homelander has provided
evidence of crimes
committed by Stan Edgar.
Vicky. I'm glad you chose
your own kind.
If we need to fight him.
- will you help me?
- Okay. I'm in.
A-Train told me
about your little plots.
Alex! Oh. my God.
- What's B.C.L. RED?
- The thing that killed Soldier Boy.
Hello. hello.
You must be Nina.
I'm after a particular weapon.
We just got to do
a little job for her.
I want to try something.
It's not power.
It's punishment.
Evening. cunts.
Why did you do this
to yourself on purpose?
You're better than this. kid.
Soldier Boy.
Ain't no team for me to hold
together no more. Butcher.
- Hold her head up. Frenchie.
- Mon coeur!
Are you recording?
Yes.
As you know.
the subject's skin has
demonstrated
remarkable durability.
Which includes internal tissue.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
How is she?
Stable. for now.
Please note that. due to
the procedure dated January 24.
the subject still registers
high radiation levels.
How the fuck's
that cunt still breathing?
Twenty sieverts of radiation.
Sulfuric acid cocktails.
More or less shoved Chernobyl
right up his arse.
We will now determine
whether his cornea
shares a similar strength.
I'll wager that's how he got
them nasty new powers.
Listen. mate.
we can't hang about here
looking for him. right?
He's Ivan's problem now.
We got to get Kimiko home
to a proper doctor.
You don't give a shit
about Kimiko.
Or anyone else.
Oh. come off it. mate.
Look. I took a fucking drug.
And in case you forgot.
I just saved your life.
You killed Gunpowder.
didn't you?
Did you use
your little laser eyes?
You're too fucking right. I did.
And it felt good.
For once. I leveled
the fucking playing field.
Butcher.
the whole point of what we do.
the whole goddamn point.
is that no one should have
that kind of power.
Well. ain't that just fucking
fairies and dancing dildos. eh?
I happen to live
right down here. mate.
on planet Earth.
Oh. fuck.
Looks like Kermit the Frog
had a right wank in your mouth.
No. I'm good. okay?
So I see.
What?
Nothing.
I know
these are difficult times.
but with the greatest humility.
I accept your nomination as CEO
of Vought International.
You know. my mother
used to say. before she
died of cancer when I was 17...
Okay. Ashley. that's enough.
Let's not bring the room down.
Apologies. sir. Of course.
Hello. everyone. Sorry I'm late.
Thank you so much
for coming up to 99.
the mountain to Muhammad.
as it were.
Okay.
Seeing as it's. uh.
my very first board meeting.
I thought perhaps we'd start by.
uh. going around the room
and giving you all a chance
- to introduce yourselves.
- Bill Marsh.
And I. for one. would like
to thank you. Homelander.
for giving me the opportunity
to serve this board
at such a pivotal moment
in. uh. Vought's history.
Pat Willis. sir.
You've rid us of Stan Edgar
and restored honesty. integrity
and innovation
to this corporation.
One question.
With the changes around here.
our EBITDA margins
will drop a tiny bit.
How do you want to handle that
on the earnings call?
What's your name?
Maureen.
Is there something you want
to get off your chest. Maureen?
Sorry. sir? Wh...
Do you think
you know better than me?
I don't know.
Maybe you think you should be
sitting in my chair and...
I should be sitting
all the way down there in yours.
No. God. no. sir.
I-I'm sorry. I-I was just...
It was stupid of me.
I'm so stupid.
and you're so great.
And... uh...
Maureen. you're embarrassing
yourself. You should go.
So who's next?
We look forward
to working hand in glove
under your tremendous
and competent leadership. sir.
It was my honor
to lead Crime Analytics
for the past 13 years.
but all good things
must come to an end.
and the Vought board decided
it was time for a change.
So. allow me to introduce you
to the new
head of Crime Analytics:
the Deep.
Thank you. thank you.
Thank you for your service. Bar.
Let's hear it for Bar.
Come on. she did great.
For someone with
no practical experience.
it's amazing.
Look. it's always been
a big dream of mine
to be able to fight crime
both at sea and on land.
I'm here to tell you
that if you work hard enough.
there's nothing
you can't achieve.
Hashtag dream big.
Real big.
Because Vought'll make sure
the right man...
Er... Sorry. Barbara.
Right person. gets the job.
So. to break the ice.
we brought...
- Cupcakes.
- From Sprinkles.
- That's right.
Oh. and one more thing.
Everyone just needs
to sign up for. uh.
performance reviews.
Just a formality.
nothing to worry about.
Mmm.
You thinking of going freelance?
Watch her head. Let's go.
She'll be up
and about in no time.
We'll see you
in the morning. yeah?
Fuck you.
Hey.
You still got me.
Tragically relapsed
into an opioid addiction.
just as he was slated
to join The Seven.
Not since Len Bias
has a public figure
been lost to a drug overdose
- on the cusp of the next...
- Hey.
Um...
Hey. Come here.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
I'm so fucking sorry.
I shouldn't be here.
It's not safe for you.
I don't care. It's okay.
Hughie. Homelander killed Alex.
He fucking murdered him.
and it's all my fault.
Hey. It is not your fault.
Come here. come here. come here.
We got Charleston Chew.
We got Almond Joy.
Bit-O-Honey.
There's White Claws
in the fridge.
Some of that gross lavender
bath bomb shit in the tub.
Look. I know
this doesn't make this
any better. but I just...
Let me take care of you
for a second.
Tell me you found it.
Moscow was a dead end.
I'm sorry.
No weapon or gun or anything?
Fuck.
Then what killed Soldier Boy?
Let... You know what?
I'm gonna get you a White Claw.
Uh. Hughie?
Your arm is broken.
Where the hell is your cast?
You're-you're really
gonna want a White Claw.
Wow. All right.
Gonna have another one.
Um... Just... I'm just trying
to get a bead on what. uh.
part you're most upset about.
Is it the part where. uh.
Soldier Boy's loose in Russia.
or the part where I-I took
some temporary Compound V?
Um...
it could be both parts. Uh...
- All the parts.
- I told you right away. though. right?
That's-that's... No secrets.
That's got to be worth
some points.
You want points
for not lying to me?
I... would like to retract
that statement. Um...
Hughie. you shot up
an untested drug
from Vought.
You could've
gotten yourself killed.
We don't have any more.
And even if we did.
I-I wouldn't take it.
It was awful.
Like. uh. the hangover.
all of it. just...
absolutely hated it.
- You loved it.
- I fucking really loved it.
It was awesome.
I mean. you know me.
If a guy in the car next to me
gives me a dirty look.
I'm like fucking
Dom Torreto taking off.
trying to get away from him
'cause I'm quick
and I'm all about family.
But in Russia...
I wasn't scared.
I-I... I saved M.M.
Me.
I could. like. teleport.
- Teleport?
- Yeah. I-I just...
I knew how to do it.
I just clenched my butt.
and-and I jumped. and...
No. Hughie. that was
stupid and dangerous.
I can't lose you. too.
Oh. God. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. You're right.
It's over.
So...
what do we do now?
I don't know.
But whatever it is.
we'll figure it out together.
You and me
against the world. right?
I love you.
I love you. too.
How the fuck is
Soldier Boy still alive?
Another nutter loose
in the world. thanks to us.
You look like warmed-over shit.
Well... least I'll be sober
in the morning.
You'll still be a Supe.
Well. if Supes
are so fucking vile.
why do you want to be one again?
What are you
gonna do with those?
No. thanks.
I've been sober
four months. asshole.
It's been a year for me.
What about Homelander's son?
No.
Be years before
Ryan can take him on.
What about that plane video?
I mean. I know it wouldn't be
so brilliant for you.
but...
least it'll pull back
the curtain on the cunt.
Would send him over the edge.
He'd end up killing
a million people.
The video was always a bluff.
Not to me it ain't.
I thought I hated the guy.
I done them all.
Coke. E. meth. smack.
Ain't nothing like this.
Used to be months of leg work
to take down a Supe.
Gunpowder...
not even a New York minute.
Must've felt good.
I hated every second.
No.
The V just made me more...
...me.
With great power
comes the absolute certainty
that you'll turn into
a right cunt.
I mean. that's the thing. right?
You're all just people.
All the V does is just
amp up all that shit
that's already inside.
Your lot? Just a bunch
of walking nuclear erections.
You know?
A-And it's not just Homelander.
I mean.
you-you fucking all got to go.
Every fucking last...
...one of you.
Yeah.
What? You still think
you're too good for me?
Chocolate limes.
For when she wakes up.
I pray she pulls through.
Ten dead Russian soldiers.
A classified lab destroyed.
Three of my contacts
in the Kremlin
have disappeared already.
You know. Sergei. there is
this absolute natural law.
That law. it says
you do not fuck me. I fuck you.
It was Monsieur Charcutier
who came to you.
made the deal with you.
Take it up with him.
I don't know him. I know you.
You're the one
who introduced us.
who pays the debt.
You work for me now.
Absolument pas.
You know. before you
abandoned me for Butcher.
you always wrung your hands.
"Oh. Nina. I cannot kill.
It's like acid to my heart."
Yet you always did.
Pyotr Semenov
and his daughter Katarina.
You do it today.
She's just a child.
That's never stopped you before.
Call me when it's done.
Mon coeur?
Mon coeur? Hey.
Ca va?
How are you feeling?
It was Soldier Boy.
Why are you smiling?
- I didn't heal!
- Hmm.
Hand me something heavy!
Something heavy!
It's too heavy!
It must've been Soldier Boy!
My powers are gone!
Can I help you?
Supersonic trusted you.
and you got him killed.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You fucking coward.
Why are you so desperate
to be with people who hate you?
Congrats from Lindsey Graham.
He's such a gooch-licker.
Anyway. I hope you know
how much Homelander
appreciates your loyalty.
Now more than ever.
he needs people he can trust.
So. to thank you
for being a team player.
Homelander has agreed to a
meeting with you and Blue Hawk.
Okay. great.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
I'll just pop outside
and get him.
What? Like. right now?
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming on such short notice. Blue Hawk.
- Oh.
A-Train.
Hey.
Big fan.
Cool. Yeah.
- Blue Hawk.
- Yeah.
I wanted to talk to you
about your patrols in Trenton.
Little excessive.
Hmm? Says who?
Well. a lot of Black folks.
No.
No. This has nothing
to do with...
...African Americans.
You and me both trained
with Coach Brink at school.
We were taught
to dominate totally.
Yeah. but
you're mostly just doing it
in-in Black neighborhoods.
And you don't want people to say
that you're being racist. right?
You know. it's actually racist
to call somebody racist.
What is this?
Is this. like. a "cancel" thing?
Am I being canceled?
What can I do
to make this right?
Wouldn't take much.
I don't know.
Make an apology or some shit.
What a great idea.
Thank you for saying that.
I'm sure Homelander would
really. really appreciate that.
Blue Hawk.
Hey. name the time and place.
It is so important
to do the work.
to have the difficult
conversations.
This is so great. you guys.
What the fuck?
Hey. buddy?
You okay. buddy?
I'm not just like
the rest of you.
I'm stronger. I'm smarter.
I'm better.
I am better!
I'm not some
weak-kneed... cry baby...
- Hey. look who it is.
- Todd.
- Hey. baby.
- Daddy!
Ah... hey!
- You ready?
- Yeah.
All right. Go get your backpack.
She can't stop talking
about this Science Center trip.
All my life.
people have tried to control me.
My whole life.
Todd. you. uh...
you got Janine
watching this guy?
I know. I know.
His language gets a bit salty.
but it's good for her.
How is this good for Janine?
Um. because he's America's
greatest hero who saves
thousands of people.
He's standing up to the crooks.
the corporations
and the legacy media.
Hey. you friend me on Facebook.
I'll send you some stuff
that will...
Todd. I don't want
Janine watching
any more of this garbage.
- Do you understand?
- Ready.
Why? Janine loves Homelander.
He's her favorite.
Isn't that right. sweetie?
'Cause Homelander is a psycho
- piece of shit. that's why.
- Daddy.
You want to pull it back in
front of the kid there. Marvin?
It's not the kid.
She's my daughter.
- Okay.
- We have breaking news this hour.
An explosion just rocked
midtown Manhattan.
Early reports indicate
19 are dead.
The NYPD and Bureau
of Superhuman Affairs...
Baby. I'm sorry.
but Daddy's got to go.
No. Daddy. I want to go
to the Science Center.
What are you doing? She's
been waiting for this all week.
Did I do something wrong?
No. baby.
I'm sorry.
The NYPD and
Bureau of Superhuman Affairs
are calling it the work
of an unknown supervillain.
At this time.
we're still waiting
for more information
from authorities...
Homelander?
Did you hear me?
Sorry. what?
I said we need
to handle this. Now.
...confirmed killed.
with dozens more injured.
Uh. yeah. of course we do. Okay.
So. book slots
on all the Sunday shows.
Tell them that. uh.
there's nothing to worry about.
not a thing.
We got everything under control.
- That's smart.
- So smart.
- So we're gonna...
- Jesus. I meant that
we need to stop this guy!
Could you watch your
fucking tone. please. darling.
I'm sorry.
I just. I mean...
Don't you think that
maybe the best way
to handle this is to find him?
I never thought of that.
Obviously.
God. O-Okay. so why don't you
go and do that?
Hmm? Run along and save the day.
Meanwhile. the grown-ups.
well. we got to worry
about the share price
and the EBITDA margins. okay?
- Thank you.
- So much.
Hey. It's me.
Tell me this isn't
who I think it is.
Probably exactly
who you think it is.
Oh. my God.
Look. we're coming
up on the site now.
Can your Crime Analytics people
look for him?
I'm on it.
Just be careful. Hughie.
Fucking hell.
Hughie.
Ivy.
Hey. uh...
Morning. morning.
- Is Vicky here?
- She's on her way.
Didn't you break your arm?
Yeah. um...
Yes. It turns out
it's a bad sprain.
- so I-I'm okay. I'll see you later.
- Okay.
Oi.
Still think
he's the Reds' problem?
All right. Easy. mate.
Fuck you.
I'll find him myself.
And what you gonna do
when you find him. eh?
He's well out
of your league. son.
You need help.
You need us.
Oh. we can talk about
what a cunt I am another time.
But right now. let's just
focus on the job at hand.
Let me help you
with Soldier Boy.
I owe you that much. and then
you don't got to see me no more.
Knowing you.
you already got a lead?
Course I fucking do.
Look at where we are.
The Legend.
Want to bet Soldier Boy
paid him a visit?
- Do you want the other half?
- No. No.
Not right now. thanks.
You were saying?
To find the guy.
we'd have to comb through
every CCTV camera in the city.
It would take a dozen analysts
working double shifts.
Okay. then let's do it.
Where is everyone?
We are everyone.
Deep fired
most of the department.
What? Why?
They had some tweets
over the years
he said were critical
of Homelander.
Said he only wants
"team players."
Can I have that half?
Thank you.
Everybody...
Reg.
What you doing here. man?
What the fuck?
- He wants to apologize.
- He came with you?
And a camera crew? Come on. man.
Listen. you get
a public apology.
Vought gets some publicity.
It's a win-win.
You just spring this shit on me?
- What's wrong with you?
- Isn't this what you wanted?
For me to use my platform
to help the community. right?
Five minutes.
All right.
Sorry. sorry.
It's the metal in my helmet.
All right.
To. uh. the residents
of Trenton.
thank you for giving me
the opportunity
to speak with you today.
As you know.
superheroes often have to make.
like. uh. split-second decisions
when fighting crime.
a-a-and I apologize
if any of mine have been...
perceived as being... racist.
But that is not who I am. okay?
Just ask my friends.
many of whom are. uh. are Black.
like A-Train.
I do not see color.
I only see crime.
And as a sign of my commitment
to you all. I am donating
$10.000 to this
community center. Thank you.
What about what you did
to Raymond Tucker?
Well. he-he-he was a criminal.
He was unarmed.
Would you have done
the same thing
to a white guy in Mill Hill?
I-I go where the crime is.
and the crime just happens
to be i-in Black neighborhoods.
That-That's not my fault.
All right. all right.
No. that's enough here.
We're done here.
Just say you're sorry.
and we can get out of here.
Yeah.
You know what? Do your research.
Like. Blacks commit
a disproportionate
number of murders.
How about all the Black men
you murdered?
How about you tell me why were
they so fucking aggressive?!
I was acting in self-defense.
You got powers! They don't!
- Black lives matter!
- Fuck you. Blue Hawk!
Walk away. walk away.
Where you going?
Get the fuck out.
- Come on. out!
- All lives matter.
- Black lives matter. motherfucker!
Supe lives matter.
Supe lives matter!
you fucking ingrates!
Hey. Blue Hawk!
Shut the fuck up!
Fuck out of here!
- Shit!
- Stupid fucks!
Shut the f...
Get the fuck out of here!
Stop!
Oh. my God!
Why?!
Nate?
Nate!
Just leave it.
What?
Leave the goddamn
clams casino at the door.
This ain't Grubhub.
motherfucker. Open up.
Marvin. Hey.
I see you still got this piece
of dog shit stuck to your boot.
Oh. go do one.
you withered old cunt.
This is Hughie.
Hughie. you know who this is?
He doesn't know who I am?
Read a fucking book. kid.
This... this is The Legend.
That's. uh. quite a nickname.
No. it's not a name.
It's a level.
Legend. we need to talk.
- Not him.
- He'll behave.
You got my word.
This is important.
and you owe me.
Whoa.
Is that you and Roy Scheider?
That's at the Chateau
after the Marathon Man premiere.
Roy Scheider. Dustin.
Anjelica. Big Chief Apache.
That whole night's
a little cloudy to me.
But if you ask Army Archerd.
I was balls deep
in Golden Geisha.
and Marlon Brando
was apparently balls deep in me.
What?
That's gay now?
Fuck you. Who cares?
What's the difference?
Anyway. after that.
I got Marlon to cut his quote
on that Steel Knight picture.
so I ask you.
who fucked who?
He was here. wasn't he?
Hmm?
Oh. no. I'm-I'm good.
I'm-I'm full. Of cocaine.
All right.
See. now Vought
is all demo points
and audience testing.
thanks to those
backstabbing fucks
Edgar and Still well.
And yes. I know she's dead.
- Fuck her anyway.
- So. The Legend was
the VP of Hero Management
over at Vought
before Still well came in.
He helps us out
from time to time.
He really doesn't know who I am?
See. when I was in charge.
you go with your gut.
That's when heroes were heroes.
not these stage-managed
silicone dolls.
I've never even seen
Homelander sweat.
let alone butter churn
half the cast of Falcon Crest
at the Beverly Hills Hotel.
which I did.
Two words.
Shannon Tweed.
Legend.
Soldier Boy came to see you.
- I need to know what he said.
- What are you. crazy?
Marvin. he's a fucking doornail.
So who's that coke for?
That's just me.
I'm writing my memoir.
It's gonna be really dynamite.
So I'm. you know.
I'm burning the candle
at both ends. I swear.
I swear on my kids' lives.
You hate your fucking kids.
So would you if you met them.
So. if I ran
the prints on that mirror.
who would I come up with?
- Huh.
- Don't worry.
Soldier Boy's not gonna trace
this back to you. Trust me.
Oh. trust you.
Like I trusted him?
You forget what happened
last time I helped?
- The underage hooker sting on Electroshock?
- Oh. Oh.
You can't trust a man like that.
Everything and everyone
he touches turns to shit.
Well. you can trust me
to bash your fucking brains out
with that leg. mate.
Butcher. please.
Look. I'm the one you trust.
Now. you know what Soldier Boy
did to my family.
And you know
because you okayed the cover-up.
Shit. I... I okayed
a million cover-ups.
And they're all tearing you up.
So just make this one right.
will you?
I thought
I was staring at a ghost.
but it was him.
He had a fucked-up beard. maybe.
- but he hadn't aged a day.
- Wait. so he doesn't get old?
- Like Storm front?
- We kept that under wraps.
Though it got a little fishy
when he starred
in that Love and War picture
with Phoebe Cates.
He was 63. She was 19.
Oh. fuck. Remember Entrapment?
Connery banged Zeta-Jones.
He was. like. a thousand.
Why was Soldier Boy here?
Came to pick up his super suit.
I held on to it.
You know me. I'm sentimental.
Although I did actually wear
the suit once
for Kelly LeBrock.
By the way. her. too.
You don't know Kelly LeBrock?
Fucking Google it.
Big "L." Big "B."
The other letters. small.
So. did he tell you
where he was going next?
Or that he was gonna blow up
a fucking restaurant on 59th?
Who the hell knows
why talent does what they do?
That's why they're talent.
He also came
for his girlfriend's address.
He's headed there.
Crimson Countess?
Why?
I didn't get the feeling
it was gonna be a happy reunion.
but I don't know.
Maybe you can go there
and find out.
But mostly.
get the fuck out of here.
Today's attack
- on 59th Street.
- Yeah.
How great a threat
is America facing?
Oh. no threat whatsoever.
No. Truly. i-it is a stretch
to even call this guy
a supervillain.
The Storm chasers.
Stormfront's supporters.
said on 4chan
that this whole thing
was an attempt by Stan Edgar
to discredit you.
Right. Yeah.
Well. look. I-I don't know
anything about Storm chasers.
but. uh. look. I can understand
why they might think that.
The minute we free Vought
of the corruption
and the lies. and this happens.
I mean. the timing
is. uh. very convenient.
Smells like a false flag.
Well. you said it. pal. not me.
And what do you say
to the mayor who wants to. uh.
impose a citywide curfew
until the terrorists
- are captured?
- Oh. please.
America is safe.
Okay? It is safe.
So. everyone. get out there.
Go to your restaurants
and. uh.
go to your movie theaters
and-and live your lives.
Have fun. okay?
You think it really
was Edgar and the mayor?
Maybe Jake Tapper.
Trying to fuck with me?
Make me look ridiculous?
Or maybe
you're just
a paranoid. malignant narcissist
who thinks
everything is about you.
Mm. it's not paranoia
if they're really
out to get you. though.
And you. Maeve.
You're out to get me.
aren't you?
What are you talking about?
William Butcher.
I can smell him all over you.
You really will do anything
to hurt me. won't you?
So...
what are you and William
cooking up?
Hmm?
Maybe you two brought
that supervillain to town.
Oh. John.
John. come on.
You're talking crazy.
I'm not cooking anything up with Butcher.
Let's talk about this.
Don't you dare
fucking "John" me.
You're not gonna weasel
your way out of this.
You know the real tragic thing
in all of this?
It's that. more than anyone.
I knew what it was like for you.
Swarmed everywhere we went.
Every little mistake.
front-page news.
It is lonely at the top. yes.
but at least we had each other.
We were lonely together.
And I loved you.
In my own way.
But you...
What happened?
Was anything about us ever real?
Hmm?
From the start.
I hated you.
But what's more.
I fucking pitied you.
You're completely
and utterly alone.
You're getting old and bitter.
You pity me?
I mean.
that's actually kind of funny.
don't you think?
Hey.
You want to know
something else that's funny?
Frenchie's not answering.
Kimiko's out of commission.
Soldier Boy's
already got a head start.
We gonna need some backup.
And here it is.
I thought you were out.
Nipped into the Duane Reade.
got some more. didn't I?
Look. I know how you feel
about this shite.
but it's Soldier Boy.
So why don't you come down
off your high horse
just this once. eh?
- My dad wouldn't want it.
- Your dad.
who died of a dodgy ticker.
suing Vought
and never getting nowhere?
Yeah. Him.
You know. he also said.
if you don't draw
the line somewhere.
how the hell are you gonna know
where you stand?
They ain't drawing no line.
Which is why we got to.
I'm in. Give me some.
Kid. didn't you just hear
a goddamn word I said?
I mean. who do you guys want?
Do you guys w-want
gawky. weak.
freaking-the-fuck-out Hughie
or do you want
strong. confident.
handling-his-shit Hughie?
With it. I can actually help.
Without it. I'm...
I-I'm probably dead.
Lad can think for himself.
- I am so sorry. Ms. Barrett.
- What the fuck
- did he do to Maeve?
- That's all right. Gregory.
Maeve is at the Global Wellness
Retreat in Malibu.
Asking for help.
it's just not easy.
And she is just truly
Brave Maeve. isn't she?
Mm-hmm. I want to speak
to her right now.
Unfortunately. the facility
requires a digital detox
for their patients. but I'm sure
you can leave her a message.
Goddamn it. Ashley!
- We can't let him do this.
- Who are you referring to?
He is out of control.
Yesterday. it was Supersonic.
Today. it's Maeve.
Tomorrow. maybe it's me or you.
Look. I know you're scared.
I am. too. but this CEO job.
it can't be worth your life.
Oh.
I don't have powers.
You don't need powers.
You just need to be human.
Please. Where is Maeve?
Is she even alive?
Look. Starlight. sh...
I am CEO.
Next time.
make a fucking appointment.
There's been severe damage
to the thoracic and lumbar
regions of the spine.
Lacerations to vertebrae
T6. T7. T8 and T9.
The damage is so severe that
Nathan will never walk again...
...individual
reached for his gun
and I had to act quickly
to save innocent lives.
You know. to think that
my donation to this community
would be met
with such intolerance.
you know. by a few Antifa thugs
and bad apples.
just breaks my heart.
Just breaks it.
I...
I got... rhythm.
Doctor. come!
She speaks!
Oh. I think I need café.
You want café?
Well. yeah. I'll be right back.
I've already got commitments
from the orangutan
from Dunst on Checks In
and the capuchin from Outbreak.
Technically.
those aren't chimps.
No. but they're famous.
They're gonna be real draws.
I worked with that
Outbreak monkey once.
- He's very good.
- I'm telling you.
there is no other place
in the world
a monkey will want to be
than right here.
Uh. I love our little chats.
you know.
but. you know.
meter's running. so...
Hold your horses.
Sir-Cums-A-Lot779.
Yes. Countess.
- Did you get them?
- Sure did.
Wow.
Those are much bigger
than I thought they would be.
Let's warm these bad boys up.
and I'll get out
of this itchy suit.
Get ready.
God. it hits the spot
every time.
Fucking sexy.
- You like that?
- Yeah.
You want it?
I'm ready.
Get that spandex down and start
popping those things in there.
Yeah.
What the fuck?!
Oh. no!
What the hell?!
Where'd you go?
I'm almost...
Hello?
Probably not the dom-sub rumble
you fancied tonight. yeah?
What the fuck's up with him?
We ain't here to hurt you.
But I am gonna
tell you something.
and I don't want you
to lose your shit.
What?
Your lover boy's
on his way here.
Soldier Boy.
He's alive.
How'd he escape from Russia?
Well. that's interesting.
You knew the Ivans had him
all this time?
I got to get out of here. Okay.
Untie me right now.
He's gonna kill me.
He's gonna kill all of us.
Why?
What'd you do?
Fuck you. all right?
Let me go or we're all dead.
Trouble in paradise. eh?
Don't you worry. darling.
We got to big fish to hook.
and you're the worm.
Is this a joke? Is this a joke?
Come on. Let me go.
Come on. guys. Let me go.
Come on. guys.
Thanks. Here.
We're sure halothane will work?
Looked that way
in the Reds' video.
We knock him out.
we keep him out.
then we figure out
what to do with him.
What the hell's going on?
Annie. what are you doing here?
M.M. called me.
- Did he?
- Just told her
we might need some backup.
That's all.
Look. y-you shouldn't be here.
all right? It's dangerous.
It's too dangerous for me?
- What about you?
- Oi. you lot.
take your little tiff
somewhere else.
We're on the job here.
Okay. uh. over here. Huh?
I just don't understand why
you wouldn't call me for this.
Okay. okay. Look. you...
you're probably gonna be mad...
...but I promised
no more secrets. right? So...
Oh. my God.
Hughie.
Hold... One second.
- You found more V?
- It's temporary V.
It's temporary. okay?
I'm not an idiot.
I-I know it's sketchy.
I've seen Trainspotting.
But i-it's Soldier Boy.
I mean. what else
was I supposed to do?
- You were supposed to call me.
- Yeah. and what if you got hurt
trying to save me. Annie?
I would never forgive myself.
But now you don't have to. okay?
I can handle myself.
I can finally save you for once.
I don't need you
to save me. Hughie.
I need you.
What'd you do?
I know you're never
gonna forgive me.
but you left me no choice.
Why?
I can't draw no line. M.
Not with what I got to do.
I'm sorry.
You'll be all right
in the morning.
You're that asshole
from the lab.
That's right.
I'm the arsehole
that let you out.
Russian Porta-Loos. eh?
You want the Countess's head
on a spike. don't you?
Well. she's in there.
yours for the taking.
Consider it a gesture
of good faith.
Good faith for what?
I was thinking that you and I
could come
to a little arrangement.
What you lot call...
a team up.
Ben?
Is that really you?
You look so young.
You don't.
I'm so. so sorry.
It wasn't my idea.
God. you got to
believe me. I-I...
How much did
the Russians pay you?
Hmm?
They didn't.
What?
They didn't pay you anything?
I loved you.
All those years...
...that they burned me
and that they pumped me
full of poison.
I held onto the hope
that you would come.
That you would save me.
Because I still loved you.
I didn't love you.
I hated you.
We all did.
Annie. please. just go.
Let us handle this.
You can yell at me...
What happened? Is he hurt?
Keep an eye on him.
He's had four or five mgs
of Rohypnol.
You fucking roofied him?!
What are you doing?
Annie. listen.
We wanted a weapon.
Soldier Boy's our weapon.
He's how we kill Homelander.
And Neuman maybe.
If anyone's strong enough.
he is.
Y-You knew Butcher
was gonna do this?
M.M. never would've
gone for it. and you...
- Look. you weren't supposed to be here.
- Oh.
So...
no more secrets. huh?
Hughie...
you're teaming up
with a murderer.
This is the only way that I can
save you from Homelander.
I'm doing this for you.
Whatever it takes. remember?
Come with us.
You and me against the world.
Hughie.
Please don't go.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today